Guide to the Office of the Chancellor and Executive Vice President 1952-1966 RG 6.0
New York University Libraries, Publisher
- Series II: John E. Ivey, Jr.
  - Subseries O: Students
    - Foreign Student Center, 1957-1959; bar code: 3 1142 042254980 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Freshmen Orientation, 1957-1958; bar code: 3 1142 042254980 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Gould Student Center, 1957-1958; bar code: 3 1142 042254980 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Loeb Student Center, 1957-1959; bar code: 3 1142 042254980 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Protestant Student Center, 1958; bar code: 3 1142 042254980 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Student Affairs, 1957-1959; bar code: 3 1142 042254980 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Student Affairs, 1957-1959; bar code: 3 1142 042254980 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Student Problems, 1957-1959; bar code: 3 1142 042254998 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Student Problems, 1957-1959; bar code: 3 1142 042254998 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Subseries P: Television, Educational
    - NYU College of the Air, undated; bar code: 3 1142 042254998 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Progress Report on Educational Organization and Program, 1957-1959; bar code: 3 1142 042254998 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Closed Circuit TV (Fund for Advancement of Education), 1957-1959; bar code: 3 1142 042254998 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Educational Television General File, 1957-1959; bar code: 3 1142 042254998 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - College for Independent Study, 1957-1959; bar code: 3 1142 042254998 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Metropolitan Educational Television Association (META), 1957-1959; bar code: 3 1142 042254998 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Sunrise Semester, 1957-1959; bar code: 3 1142 042254998 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Sunrise Semester, 1957-1959; bar code: 3 1142 042254998 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Series III: George D. Stoddard, 1960-1964
  George D. Stoddard's appointment by the Board of Trustees as Executive Vice-President took place on January 25, 1960 during the tenure of President Carroll V. Newsom (1956-62). Stoddard had directed the exhaustive Self-Studx, published 1956, which redefined NYU's educational mission and constituency. He played a central role in constructing a new hierarchy of administrative offices that centralized educational policy and budgetary control, and in 1960 assumed the office he helped design, the second-highest at NYU.
  During Stoddard's tenure, the university expanded traditional instruction within the schools and fostered innovative programs in order to draw new students, such as the Communications Art Group (Box 11:3) and television instruction (Boxes 9:8, 13:8, 9). The university experimented with international programs and cooperative education abroad (Box 6, passim) while relationships with federal and state governments grew more diverse and complex. Stoddard associated himself with expansion of the Washington Square campus through renovation and construction, and several files in Boxes 8 and 17 are concerned with space utilization and new construction; see Box 17 for files on the construction of Warren Weaver Hall and the Courant Center. Wholly new programs appeared during his term of office, including recruitment and training for the Peace Corps (Box 17: 11,12) and a new level of concern for on campus student health services (Box 13:10,11 and 18: 4). Of particular interest is Stoddard’s attention and response to preservation of the university's faculty, student, and operating records dating from 1962, the year in which major cities in the United States were being menaced by Russian missiles based in Cuba.
  Within the general correspondence files (Box 5:12, 13) is correspondence regarding increasing levels of crime around the Height campus in 1959-60 and its effect on faculty and students. Those files also contain restricted materials concerning a troubled student and a graduate whose credentials were questioned. The University College file (Box 8:7) contains a tentative policy statement of February, 1960, regarding the education of women at the Heights campus. Stoddard's tenure spanned the period in which Newsom left office and James M. Hester became President in 1960.
  The records are arranged in four series that reflect the four years of his tenure, and each series is arranged alphabetically. The sub-heoings are not uniform for all the series because new topical headings presented themselves as the office and its responsibilities elaborated the record-keeping system, and care must be exercised when searching for like files and like subjects within the four series. Some files appear to be incomplete, and the earliest files, some dating from 1957, date from prior administrations. This subgroup has been rearranged and refoldered by the supervising archivist, who discarded the folder dates because they were inaccurate and misleading. A few files are restricted that contain records of faculty discipline and tenure cases and an ROTC commission declination.
  - Subseries A: 1959-1961
    - Sub-Subseries A: Administration
      - Contract Officer, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255276 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Voorhis, Harold O. - Vice-President and Secretary, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255276 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - University Development - Vice-President General Frank Howley, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255276 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - President, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255276 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Office of Institutional Research - J.D. Russell, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255276 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Office of Institutional Research - J.D. Russell, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255276 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Sub-Subseries B: Admissions and Registration
      - Registration and Financial Aid, Dean of - E.C. Kastner, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255276 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Admissions Office (F. Crossland), 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255276 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Admissions Office (F. Crossland), 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255276 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Registrar, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255276 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Sub-Subseries C: All-University Departments
      - Biology, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255276 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Chemistry, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255276 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - Classics, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255276 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - Economics, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255276 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      - English, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255276 (Box 53, Folder 15)
      - Geology, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255276 (Box 53, Folder 16)
      - German, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255276 (Box 53, Folder 17)
      - Government, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - History, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - Mathematics, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - Music, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - Philosophy, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - Physics, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - Psychology, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - Romance Languages, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - All-University Department Heads - Senate Committee, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Sociology, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Sub-Subseries D: Committees
      - Committee for Civilian Protection at Washington Square Center, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - Membership and Donors, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - Nursing Education, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - Nursing Education, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - Research Advisory Council, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 15)
      - Committee on Selective Service, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Sub-Subseries E: Foundations
      - Marshall Foundation, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 17)
      - Relm Foundation, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 18)
      - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Sub-Subseries F: Government
      - ROTC, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 20)
      - ROTC, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255284 (Box 54, Folder 21)
      - State Education Department, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255292 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - State Education Department, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255292 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Sub-Subseries G: International Affairs
      - Hispanic-American Affairs, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255292 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Mediterranean Research Group, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255292 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Netherlands Summer Session, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255292 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - Center for International Affairs, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255292 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - Center for International Affairs, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255292 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - Center for International Affairs, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255292 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Sub-Subseries H: Miscellaneous
      - University Representation at Miscellaneous Conferences, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255292 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - Cooperative Education Study, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255292 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - International Education Exchange Program, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255292 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - New York University Glee Club, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255292 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - Trimester Plan, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255292 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Sub-Subseries I: Schools
      - Athletics, Division of, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255292 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      - Commerce, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255292 (Box 55, Folder 15)
      - Dentistry, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255292 (Box 55, Folder 16)
      - Education, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255292 (Box 55, Folder 17)
      - Education, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255292 (Box 55, Folder 18)
      - Engineering, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255292 (Box 55, Folder 19)
      - Fine Arts, Institute of, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Division of General Education, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Graduate School of Arts and Science, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Graduate School of Social Work, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - La Maison Francaise, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Law, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Medicine, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - Retailing, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - University College of Arts and Science, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - Washington Square College of Arts and Science, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Sub-Subseries J: Special Projects
      - Bard College, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      - Center for Applied Social Research, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 14)
      - Free Europe Committee, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 15)
      - Office of Naval Research, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 16)
      - Patterson Moos Research, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 17)
      - World Trade Center, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 18)
      - Dean of Students, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Sub-Subseries K: Television
      - Metropolitan Education Television Association (META), 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 20)
      - All-University TV Committee, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 21)
      - RCA Workshop - Center for Instructional TV, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 22)
      - RCA Workshop - Center for Instructional TV, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Sub-Subseries L: Undesignated
      - Dramatic Art (Washington Square), 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 24)
      - Undesignated Funds Form, 1959-1960; bar code: 3 1142 042255300 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Subseries B: 1960 - 1961
    - Administration - Ad Hoc Committee on Monthly Tuition, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255318 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Administration - Ad Hoc Committee on Student Counseling, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255318 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Administration - Business Office, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255318 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Administration - Coordinator of Research Services (Sidney G. Roth), 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255318 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Administration - Office of Institutional Research, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255318 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Administration - University Relations (Arthur Brandon), 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255318 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Administration - Vice-President and Secretary (Harold O. Voorhis), 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255318 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Admission, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255318 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Coordinating Committee - Teaching of Liberal Arts and Sciences, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255318 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Appointments, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255318 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Foundations - Advancement of Education, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255318 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255318 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255318 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Government - International Cooperative and Administration, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255318 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Government - National Science Foundation, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255318 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Government - U. S. Office of Education, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255318 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Hofstra College, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255318 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - International - African Conference, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255326 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - International - African Fair, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255326 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - International - African Scholarship Program, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255326 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - International - African Trip, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255326 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - International - Brazil Institute, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255326 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - International - Brazil Institute, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255326 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - International - Center for International Affairs, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255326 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - International - Institute for International Education, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255326 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - International - Israel Workshop, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255326 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - International - Spanish Institute, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255326 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - International - West Indies, University of, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255326 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Retirement - TIAA/CREF Retirement Plan, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255326 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Schools - Athletics, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255334 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Schools - Commerce, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255334 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Schools - Communication Arts Group, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255334 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Schools - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255334 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Schools - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255334 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Schools - Dentistry, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255334 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Schools - Education, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255334 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Schools - Education, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255334 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Schools - Education, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255334 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Schools - Art Education Department, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255334 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Schools - Engineering, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255334 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Schools - General Education, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255334 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Arts and Science, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255334 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255334 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255334 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Schools - Law, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255342 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Schools - Mathematical Sciences, Institute of, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255342 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Schools - Mathematical Sciences, Institute of, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255342 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Schools - Mathematical Sciences, Institute of, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255342 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Schools - Mathematical Sciences, Institute of, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255342 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Schools - Medical College, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255342 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Schools - University College, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255342 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Schools - Washington Square College, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255342 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Space - Stoddard Horner Group, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255342 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Space - Task Force on Space, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255342 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Space - Washington Square Committee, Space Allocation, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255342 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Space - Washington Square Southeast Project, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255342 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Special Projects - Aging Study, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255359 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Special Projects - Albany Program, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255359 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Special Projects - Bell Telephone/Engineering Program, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255359 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Special Projects - Ellis Island, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255359 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Special Projects - French and American Sciences, Symposium, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255359 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Special Projects - Loeb Student Center, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255359 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Special Projects - Puerto Rico Project, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255359 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Special Projects - Television Instruction, 1960-1961; bar code: 3 1142 042255359 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Subseries C: 1961 - 1962
    - Administration - Business Office, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255359 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Administration - President, Office of, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255359 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Administration - Research Services, Office of, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255359 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Administration - Secretary, Office of, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255359 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Administration - Trustees, Board of, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255359 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Admissions, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255359 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Admissions and Registration, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255359 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Admissions - Registrar, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255359 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Associations - American Council of Education, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255359 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Committees - Appointments, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255367 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Committees - Scholarship Regulation, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255367 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Committees - School of Arts and Science, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255367 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Appointments, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255367 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Prospects, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255367 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Fundraising, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255367 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - General Education, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255367 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Government - New York State (Education) Department, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255367 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Government - U.S. Air Force, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255367 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Government - U.S. Army, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255367 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - International - Iranian Project, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255367 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - International - Universities (Japan, Nigeria, Ghana), 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255367 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Libraries, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255375 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Schools - Athletics, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255375 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Schools - College of Arts and Science, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255375 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Schools - Communications Arts Group, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255375 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Schools - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255375 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Schools - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255375 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Schools - Dentistry, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255375 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Schools - Education, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255375 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Schools - Education (School for Children), 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255375 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Schools - Engineering, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255375 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Schools - General Education, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255375 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Arts and Science, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255375 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255375 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255383 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Social Work, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255383 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Schools - Institute of Fine Arts, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255383 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Schools - Institute of Hebrew Studies, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255383 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Schools - La Maison Francaise, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255383 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Schools - Law, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255383 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Schools - Medical, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255383 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Schools - Retailing, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255383 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Schools - Town Hall, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255383 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Schools - University College, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255383 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Schools - Washington Square College, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255383 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Space - Planning Group (School for Children), 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255383 (Box 64, Folder 12)